As Prophet T.B Joshua ministers powerful prayers and deliverance in the name of Jesus,
as God Almighty uses the faculties of Prophet TB Joshua
to expose and expell all agents of darkness operating in the lives of people -
watch what happens to this woman as she receives a Spirit filled touch
from the Man of God.
Go, how many are you?
We are 36.
You say what?
Who is number 1?
Snake!
Number two!
Fish!
Number three!
Anaconda!
Number four!
Serpent!
Who else? Who else?
Queen of the coast!
What have you done to her affection?
We chained her, she has no feelings for men.
She is used to destroy.
How did you enter her?
I entered her, when she was 8 years old.
What else do you push her to do?
I push her to destroy many things.
And what else?
She destroyed her family, she cannot stay in her husband's house.
What is the meaning of this chain?
It's from our kingdom, they said, I should be putting it.
For what?
To attract men.
Emmanuel!
My name is Flora Ruth Akinpelumi.
I was born and brought up in Niger State but I came from Ondo town.
All this started... I just want to thank God for what He has done in my life.
God delivered me from the power of a powerful snake called Annaconda.
The spirit of python, lion, fish, green, blue, black, many kind of snakes -
36 in number inside of me.
So all this started, when I was 8 years old, in Niger State.
My mummy took us to a river called Sharabash to wash plates and clothes.
When we got to the stream, we washed the clothes and plates,
and my mum asked us to take our baths. Then we bathed inside the stream.
Then later on I saw a form of a boat and then I climbed onto that boat.
And I was bathing.
Then later on I felt my body changed. I was heavy and I was so tired inside of me.
Then my mummy said I am going extreme to the water and I should come out of the water.
So whilst you were actually bathing in the water, you physically felt as if something entered inside of you?
I felt, when I was bathing on that board - something entered me,
and I felt so heavy and tired, I didn't know what I was doing again.
Then my mummy said we should come out from the water, which I did.
We were taken back home, then I went straight to my room and I fell on the bed and I slept off.
Then the next morning I woke up and I felt so tired. My brothers and sisters had dressed for school
but I told my mom that I cannot go to school because I don't understand myself.
Then I asked her that: "Mommy, I am hungry and I need something to eat."
She gave me a plate of rice. I finished it. I demanded for another plate.
I finished it. I demanded for another one and finished it.
Then she asked me: what is really wrong with me?
I said it looks as if that food that I am eating - something is inside me that is eating that food.
That I don't get myself.
Since then the spirit inside me started creating more problems in the family.
Okay sister, so we just want to understand clearly.
You said that your first experience was that you began eating excessively.
As if there was something within you that was actually taking that food.
And after that what was the next experience you had spiritually
that made you realize that this demon had really entered inside of you?
I felt weak and heavy, so tired.
Whenever I ate that food, something inside of me like strings in my tummy.
Then I felt that something is eating the food in my stomach.
Since then I started acting strangely in the family.
Sometimes my mommy will talk to me. I will not even listen to her.
I just want to be myself, I just want to do things in my own.
Then, from that dream, when I dreamt that a big snake entered into my private part -
big snake entered into my private part -
since then, if I am sleeping, I will be feeling sexy and will be sexing in the dream
and flying all over the place. Sometimes I used to fly all over the world.
I used to fly to many places, I travelled out and I even went to market
buying things from old women. Since then things started changing.
So you are talking about what was happening in the dream after the experience, when this demon entered you,
a snake entered you through your private parts -
and you began to have all these experiences in the dream.
Now physically, as you were growing up, what began to happen to you as you got a little bit
more mature and this spirit began to operate in your life?
When I got to the age of 15, that snake inside of me told me everything to do.
If maybe I am going on the way, it directed me to a shop -
that is my people in the other realm are the ones that own that shop.
When you say 'my people', can you just explain what you mean by that?
That is my colleagues in the other realm, the other kingdom.
They directed me to the shops to get some weaves and clothes to attract men.
Some of those clothes and weaves I put on just to attract men.
And those chains and earrings. They described the shops:
that go to this shop, get these clothes, get this weave so that when you put on,
when men see you - they will be seduced and attracted to you.
And not only men, even ladies too were attracted whenever I put all these things on.
Okay, so in the dream in the spiritual world you were directed to go to
a physical shop and purchase some items that were then used
as a means of seducing men and also attracting people to you.
So when you now went to the shops and bought those items, where agents from
that kingdom were actually operating, you now started wearing those things and
using then - what began to happen?
When I put those things on, my friends will say: "Baby, you are sweet", and this and that.
"Can you accompany us to a party, a club?" Then I will go with them to the club.
So in the spirit in the other realm I am a Princess called "The queen of the coast".
I have a position there as a leader and we have this big spiritual band.
Whenever they want to do anything
gathering or party, they will call me
that I should come out to dance.
After dancing - the way I used to dance in the other realm - in the physical I will dance - the same way
that I dance in the spiritual realm - with my friends in the club.
If I am dancing my dance, they will just give me the sign on how to twist and seduce man with dance.
So many men will be attracted, when I am dancing and from there some of the guys really wanted me.
Some even come there with their girlfriends but when they see
that I am flowing and dancing - those dances will seduce them and they will start fighting,
push their girlfriends that: "No, no, no, I don't want you anymore."
They will now come to me because of that dance and say: "Baby, please, can you dance more?"
Then I will dance for them. They start fighting because of me.
Then I have to run away from that place because I dont wan't to be bruised.
Then I run out from that place.
So the men that you end up seducing, and then going out to meet them -
just tell us, what will happen when you meet with those men, and then
what will then happen in their lives as a consequence of this?
Yes, it's good for the men that don't hear...
You know what, the snake that entered me cause commotion.
Any man that sleep with me will never say: "No, I am going. I will stay, please give me more
because you are sweet". But they never knew that they are sleeping with a snake.
They fix it in the mouth of the snake. So the snake will take the sperm to the other kingdom,
and we use the sperm to make increase of my wealth and riches.
On the other side I have so many houses, I have cars and many other things.
I have gold, I have dollars and I have millions.
Okay, now sister you are talking about spiritual here, that when you sleep with men,
that spirit of snake within you is actually the person those men are sleeping with and
that spirit will take the sperm; now physically, what would now happen to such men?
Perhaps maybe they are business men or they are married men, what would happen to them
as a result of encountering you and sleeping with you?
Those men that slept with me, some got compassion from me.
There are those that really want, maybe I feel free for them and they feel free with me. I will just let go.
But those that are hard, maybe when things are going well for them,
maybe they have money and they don't want to give me, then I will take all the wealth back,
and every blessing they have - I will take it back.
And if they are married?
If those men that meet with you are married men, once they encounter you -
what will happen to their marital lives?
Because of the affection that I have for the man and because of what the man has for me
due to the power inside of me, I lured him and drawn him from his wife.
So they will start having problems, commotion in the family and nagging,
until the husband will throw her out of the house.
Okay, so I think we have been listening to our sister. This is a lesson for those who are present here
and our viewers all over the world. Our sister is explaining that because of that demonic powers
that were within her - what would happen to men that were seduced by her, when she dances
in the night clubs and end up sleeping with her and the destruction that would actually happen
in their lives afterwards. Now, sister you mentioned that there were many different ways,
in which you were seducing men, there were some certain items that you were given.
Can you just explain to us how those items - perhaps, the chains and other things -
how they were used as a tool to attract and seduce such men?
You know, all those things I put on, you that have the physical eyes - you will not see.
But those that have spiritual eyes will see because whenever I put it on, the spirit has already
entered in it.
Okay, you are just holding something for us here. Can you just explain what you are actually holding
and just explain the function that it had in your life in the past, when you had this evil.
This chain is for mission. They sent me to put it.
So anytime I put it on my leg, my leg has already been possessed.
The leg is possessed - it's not ordinary leg. When I put it on, any man that put his eyes on my leg and on the chain
will be attracted and will come to me and ask me out.
Then I will say 'no problem'.
Okay, so we can remember that during the deliverance of our sister this was actually
the chain that was around her leg as she actually came to the Synagogue Church of All Nations.
As that was the powers of darkness that she was using at that time to destroy and really cause
a lot of commotion in many people's lives. Sister, can you continue with your confession.
Apart from the issue of destroying men, which other areas did these spirits begin to use you?
They used me in so many ways, to destroy husbands and wives,
even neighbours, to cause problems, misunderstandings.
And these spirits caused me anger - whenever I am angry, I fought with weapons, bottles and knives.
In fact there was a woman in Benin, she provoked me.Then I just used the bottle and I just passed it on her.
I wanted to stab her and then she ran away and mistakenly the bottle cut me and my blood flow
because my people want blood. Whenever the blood gushes out, I would feel calm and relieved.
My mission is accomplished.
Okay so whenever you are angry you will not calm down, until you see blood?
So you have to injure that person with the weapon for blood to flow before you calm down?
Yes.
Okay, you have mentioned some areas in your life that have become to be affected negatively.
Can you explain, apart from these men that were coming to you as you were seducing them -
what about the area of relationships and marriages on your side? Men that approached you for marriage,
just tell us what happened?
Many men asked me for marriage and those husbands that asked my hand in marriage
are the ones that the spirit pushes them to me. They are not my real husband.
Those spirits pushed them to me because they didn't want me to get married.
They just want me to be their princess, sending me on errands to do whatsoever
but due to the force to be a mother - I just wanted to be a mother and to have a baby.
Then a man came into my life. His name is Umobi, we were dating. Then I had 2 issues from him.
Blessed Samuel and Mercy. We were married together and we were staying fine,
no problem. Until one certain night I had a spiritual husband - a black and a white.
So you had two different spiritual husbands?
Yes, one is like a goliath - the black one, tall and giant. Uju was a giant goliath.
Then the other one is fair and light in complexion.
So one faithful night we were sleeping, I and my husband. The black spirit is a kind of jealousy.
It can kill, it can even stab someone because it doesn't want to see me with any man.
Even talkless of being with a man. Then one faithful night I was just sleeping on the bed.
Then I saw that spiritual husband, the giant one goliath who is very huge and black.
He just came and was standing in the corridor and woke me up. He said I should wake my husband up,
that he wanted to have fun with me. Then he tapped my husband. I saw the spiritual husband face to face,
he was standing at the door post. Then he said that I should wake my husband.
Then I tapped my husband. Then he controlled my husband and turned his memory and told him
go to this place and wait. My husband stood up and went to that place and waited.
Then the spiritual husband lied on the bed and made fun with me.
After making fun with me,
there is one kind of sharp pains it deposited in my private parts.
So when my husband wants to have fun with me I will just shout and say: "No, please I don't need you,
I don't want to have fun because that pain is pepperish."
So as a result of this, what then happened to this marriage with your two children?
The marriage crumbled and since then my husband has thrown me out and packed the children and run away.
Since then I have not set my eyes on them.
So you mean that since then you have not actually seen your husband and your two children, for how long now?
Up to four years now - four years.
So after this first encounter with your first husband, what then happened after that?
After that I ran to Ondo town and I started working there as a security in ...
Then I met a guy again, we started going out together and I got pregnant.
The same spirit that threw me out from the first one,
threw me out from the second one. Because of everything - nagging and fighting, shouting and breaking bottles.
And all said and done, he threw me out of the house.
So, you became so violent in the house and you were thrown out for the second time.
And you had a child with that man as well?
Yes.
So we can understand that apart from how the spirit was using our sister to destroy others,
it also destroyed her own life
rendering her without any husband, children from different men and her whole family scattered.
So, can you tell us, sister, in the midst of all this - how did you come to be at the SCOAN last weak?
Before I was in Lagos, I was in Ondo, and my friend called me.
She said: "Flora, can you please come down to Lagos?"
Because I was so scattered and disgust, frustrated, no job, nowhere to stay,
nobody to call upon - then I called her one day: "Please, can you help me, I need a job."
Then she said that I should come down toLlagos. Then I packed my things and came down to Lagos.
She allowed me to stay with her, then we slept on the same bed.
Sometimes she could wake me up and say: "Flora, I don't understand the way you sleep.
I don't get you, that you are not yourself, you disappear, your body -
you leave your body." Sometimes she would tap me but I couldn't wake up
until I have gone to do the assignment they have sent me.
Then I explain everything to her and she said: "Baby, please, you have to go to a
strong church so that you can be delivered from this power."
Because she knew I was not an ordinary person.
Then I asked which church she wanted me to go, then she said - Synagogue, Church of All Nations.
Then I prepared. Last weak Sunday I was here.
I was sitting outside the gallery,
when the man of God was preaching and saying
that please, some people here - what makes them not to receive their blessing,
is because they don't know how to pray.
They pray ha-ha-ha-ha and the problem is still there.
That the the only thing that you have to have when you pray - is to pray within yourself, inner yourself
as you want to pray. And there was a prayer point that was made that day.
The prayer point was that you say: "Take more of me and give me more of You."
I was meditating within myself and saying, which kind of a prayer point is this?
How can somebody take more of me and give me more of himself. I said: "God."
So I was not following them to pray that prayer
because I didn't understand this. How can somebody take more of me and give me more of him?
"Me", I said "I will not pray this prayer". Some people that were sited beside me were just looking at me
that this girl is not praying.
Then later on, the man of God repeated it again and I said: "I'm even tired, let me stand up and go back home".
That spirit said: "Stand up, take your purse and leave this place because the man of God is coming out with fire".
I said: "Fire?"
I said if it is that, I am not staying in this place.
Then, when I wanted to pick my purse, something just knock on my head
that where I am going to?
Then I turned left and right - I couldn't see the person.
Then I said: "Let me take my purse and run away".
As I wanted to take my purse and run away, something just slapped me.
Then I screamed and shouted!
Then the usher ushered me out
so I had an opportunity to be touched by the man of God.
So just to understand exactly what our sister is saying -
that was the exact moment where the prophet T.B. Joshua started the mass prayer,
and at that moment the Holy Spirit arrested our sister.
And after that we saw that you were privileged to receive prayer from prophet T.B. Joshua.
So can you just describe to us what happened, when you encountered him during that time of prayer.
When that power slapped, I don't know where that power came from,
but I know somebody slapped me on my head.
He slapped me on my head and I felt something shaking in my body
and I felt fire inside of me and I started shouting and screaming:
"Man of God don't touch me, I hate you!" before they brought me at the center church.
So when you then received prayer as seen on the screen, describe to us what happened at that point?
Man of God touched me, he touched me and I was delivered totally.
I felt something pushed out of me, I feel relief and sense, I feel relief inside me.
AMEN! Lets put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Sister, we want to understand clearly the experiences in your life after your deliverance.
Just tell us, ever since the deliverance you received last week, what are the changes you've seen
in your life to testify that that spirit has left you completely.
I feel so relieved from that deliverance. When the man of God touched me, I feel so relieved, I feel so OK.
I talk to people, I associate with them, sitting together.
I sleep like a baby, I wake up like a baby, I eat normal.
I don't dream those kind of dreams again.
Many other things like that, good things.
Before I used to be angry but today, I am not more angry.
I feel happy, I chat with others like my friends, I am free.
I am delivered, I am okay.
Amen! Lets put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
So that spirit that was formally using you go out to seduce men and dance in a way
in clubs to attract men - you no longer have interest in such things or desire to do such things?
I don't have those feelings anymore.
Even like yesterday some of those men, came to me and
said: "Please, dance for me" and I said: "I am not for those things anymore, I am a changed person."
Wow! Lets put our hands together for the Lord Jesus Christ!
Truly, the evidence of Christ Jesus is lives changed.
Now we believe our sister has a lot advice
for our viewers all over the world based on her own experiences in life,
and someone who was part of the kingdom of darkness before.
Sister, what would you like to advice people concerning your life experiences,
especially where people that, for example, used to go to clubs, men who are used to
chase after ladies, even though they are married, - what would you like to advice them
as someone who was an agent of darkness in the past?
Men that don't hear words - they miss the mark.
But those that they hear words, they have the relief.
I just want to advice the viewers not only the men but even the women, the youth,
even the children. You just have to stay away from the glitters things because " all that glitters is not gold".
You will see some ladies beautiful outside but you don't know what is inside them.
Men will just say: "Oh God, this girl is beautiful, I love her shape, she is "figure 8"
And they will start coming. So, you men, just have to be careful.
Be careful what you do outside and take time, not going out
to a party or a club drinking and any other thing, you have to stop it.
And mothers, advice your children what they put on, what they wear and where they go to.
Amen! Let us put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
And sister, we believe there are many people watching you right now and they are in the bondage.
that you were once in - and perhaps they too after listening to your experience
knowing that they too have the similar spirit that is dwelling in them or perhaps
they have encountered someone in the past that has initiated them into such.
As people who are in need of deliverance -
someone that is standing here who has been delivered right now -
what do you want to advice such people that are still in that bondage?
Those people that are still in that bondage, I just want them to open their hearts freely,
so that they can be able to be delivered.
While you are hardening your heart you are hardening your problem, you are hardening your deliverance.
But when you open your heart you will be delivered and you will be free from all those powers.
Amen! Lets put our hands together for Christ Jesus one more time!
So we thank God for our sister's life, we thank God that she has been taken in the kingdom of light.
We pray that God will give you the grace to maintain this deliverance by making the Word of God
the standard for your life and we know that as you do so, the best is yet to come, in Jesus' name!
AMEN